GEDE RICO WIJAYA

<u>LinkedIn | GitHub | gricowijaya@gmail.com | Denpasar, Bali</u>

PROFILE

I've been using Linux for Development for 3 Years. My Skills on using Linux helped the purposes for the company and team that I worked with to achieve their goals on providing service and IT Solutions for Businesses and Open Source Projects.

SKILLS

- Linux Operating System such as Debian, Ubuntu Server, Arch, CentOS
- Agile Method Development, Scrum, CI/CD Automation, GitHub Actions, GitLab CI
- Bash Scripting, Python Scripting, Node JS, Go
- Container Orchestration such as Docker Swarm, and Kubernetes
- Cloud Computing with Google Cloud and AWS

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024

Universitas Udayana - Information

Technology

• Current GPA (7th Semester) 3.87

CERTIFICATION

2022 Binar

Academy

Binar Academy Back End

2023

Associate Cloud Engineer Google

ACE Google

EXPERIENCES

March 2022 - September 2023

Engineer at Cakeplabs

Devops & Full Stack

- Led Team for Captioneer AI Project, participating in the Infrastructure Design and implementing automated deployment using GitLab CI, Google Cloud Run, Services Design, Logic Design, Frontend Implementation with Svelte JS, LLM PaLM 2 integration on FastAPI, Mapping Service with AWS Route 53 and Google Cloud DNS by dev.alterolabs.com.
- Deploying a Web Service on AWS EC2 using Docker Swarm.
- Deploy Meta LLaMa using the local on premise infrastructure for research on proprietary app and fine tuning LLM.
- Monitoring User Growth Monitoring using Metabase, Node Red Bot for notification on Mattermost, Monitoring BI Data using Grafana and MySQL.
- Implement Meta API with Node Red for Sales on property.

February 2023 - August 2023

DevOps & Back End Engineer on

Google Bangkit 2023 I

- Led Team for RENATA (Restorasi Tumbuhan dan Tanah) Project.
- Participating in the Infrastructure Design using <u>Terraform</u>.
- Implementing automated scalable deployment using <u>GitHub Actions</u> on <u>Google Kubernetes Engine</u>.
- LLM PaLM 2 integration using FastAPI.

August 2022 - January 2023 **Binar Academy**

DevOps & Back End Engineer on

• Led Team for Prime Flight Backend Project, Back End Systems with Express JS Framework, CI/CD with Github Actions on Railway Service, Sentry Monitoring Service.